In 3D space, you can create a 3D version of a 3D pen.
Through the new 3D pen tool, you can create a 3D version of a 3D pen directly in 3D space.
When clicking, press the Shift key to create a straight line.
On the created line, press the right key to select the length of the display or hidden line.
Press the P key to switch the pen to a 3D version in 3D space.
When creating a line, press the Ctrl key and click to create a curve.
By editing the 3D pen tool, you can adjust the position of the straight line and the curve.
When dividing the version by line,
the lines will automatically create a curve along the shared division line.
When creating a line, press the D key to switch the hidden point of the creation to the distance from the virtual model.
You can first rely on the virtual model
to draw some lines.
Then press the P key to continue drawing lines in 3D space to form a version.
Please adjust the version line by adjusting these points.
Then click the right button to delete it.
When creating a line, press the right button to create a curve along the shared division line.
When creating a line, press the right button to continue drawing lines in 3D space.
When creating a line, press the left button to extreme the curve.
poisnt this, the line can be drawn confzos.
Irish Silver
In this application, you can butts a line into the 3D space.
The sleeve panels do not need to be separated, so we can combine them.
Use the line sewing machine and the free sewing machine to sew the panels together.
When one side of the panel is finished, use the symmetrical panel, panel and sewing line tools to create the symmetrical panel on the other side.
Then sew the panels on both sides together.
Simulate and inspect your clothing.
That's all for this video.
See you next time.